<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://www.nuriatimm.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://www.nuriatimm.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-11-14T17:19:44+00:00</updated><id>https://www.nuriatimm.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Sasha Writes</title><subtitle>An amazing website.</subtitle><author><name>Nuria</name></author><entry><title type="html">Spa</title><link href="https://www.nuriatimm.com/how-to-have-a-spa-day/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Spa" /><published>2020-11-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-11-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://www.nuriatimm.com/how-to-have-a-spa-day</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.nuriatimm.com/how-to-have-a-spa-day/">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;If you want to have a spa right at home this is for you. Fill the bath tub with water maybe also some bubbles. You can set up some candles. Put on a face mask. Put some rose petals on the bubbles. Turn of the lights and you are done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><author><name>Nuria</name></author><summary type="html">How to have a Great spa day</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Covid-Free cookies</title><link href="https://www.nuriatimm.com/how-to-make-a-covid-free-cookie/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Covid-Free cookies" /><published>2020-11-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-11-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://www.nuriatimm.com/how-to%20make-a-covid-free-cookie</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.nuriatimm.com/how-to-make-a-covid-free-cookie/">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Here is how to make covid free cookies. Ingredients: store bought cookie dough or homemade, food dye,
eqiptment: roller, 2 bowls, spoon,  plastic wrap&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Steps: Split the dough to make it have one small amount dough and one big amount of dough in one of the bowls, put food diy in it and mix it. Do the same with the smaller amount of dough but with another color food diy. put the plastic wrap on a table, put the dough on it seperate from the small and the big cookie dough. Roll out both seperated doughs. roll the big amount of dough into a ball. Cut the smaller dough into strands. Put the strands onto the cookie ball all on the top. And there you have it a Covid-Free Cookie!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Nuria</name></author><summary type="html">Covid shaped cookies that tastes like cookies</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">American doll house</title><link href="https://www.nuriatimm.com/Amercan-Doll-House/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="American doll house" /><published>2020-11-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-11-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://www.nuriatimm.com/Amercan-Doll-House</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.nuriatimm.com/Amercan-Doll-House/">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;If your kid has an American doll and they want to to have an American Doll House this is the best place.  Equiptment: wall Shelf, cooling towel, pins, decorative lights, American funiture.
Steps: pin the cooling towel onto the wall shelf for cool backrounds just for decorated vibes. Put the decorative lights in the corner of the roof in the wall shelf. Then you can put the American Doll furniture where you would usally put it in the rooms where you want to put it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><author><name>Nuria</name></author><summary type="html">How to make a American Doll House</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Family pommunicates</title><link href="https://www.nuriatimm.com/family/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Family pommunicates" /><published>2020-11-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-11-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://www.nuriatimm.com/family</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.nuriatimm.com/family/">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;If you have not have much time with your family, this is for you.
Things you can do with your family is that you can watch a movie with them. You can play a family game that you will all enjoy. Also you can take turns telling a dream that happened to you or acually happend in real life. If someone is bothering you, you can say,” i don’t appeciate that.” then you can walk away and think of something else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><author><name>Nuria</name></author><summary type="html">You need to have lots of times with your family</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to have an enjoyeble life as a kid</title><link href="https://www.nuriatimm.com/How-to-have-a-great-life-as-a-kid/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to have an enjoyeble life as a kid" /><published>2020-11-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-11-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://www.nuriatimm.com/How-to-have-a-great-life-as-a-kid</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.nuriatimm.com/How-to-have-a-great-life-as-a-kid/">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Here is how to be a great kid having a awsome life. First you need to get very comfy. You can put candles in your room to have a homey vibe. Play some relaxing music. Wear some comfy clothes. You can put on a face mask.You can sit in your bed and watch a video and relax.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><author><name>Nuria</name></author><summary type="html">While being a kid be polite</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Life struggles</title><link href="https://www.nuriatimm.com/life-struggles/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Life struggles" /><published>2020-11-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-11-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://www.nuriatimm.com/life-struggles</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.nuriatimm.com/life-struggles/">&lt;p&gt;In my life i’ve had struggles, i am sure you had at least one. I will give you some struggles i’ve had, also what i did to solve it. This can help you also if you happend to have the same problem. One day I wanted to have soft and beutiful face, so i looked for a face mask cream. When i found it i put it on. When I saw the results I was in shock when i saw my face, it was red! What I did was that I washed my face then waited for the next day to make it better and heal up&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Nuria</name></author><summary type="html">i have lots of problems in my life</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Your Dads First Post</title><link href="https://www.nuriatimm.com/your-dads-first-post/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Your Dads First Post" /><published>2020-11-11T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-11-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://www.nuriatimm.com/your-dads-first-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.nuriatimm.com/your-dads-first-post/">&lt;p&gt;Hi Nuria!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is your dad writing your first post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am sure you are &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; happy about that at all!  As as soon as you learn a bit more you can write your own posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are going to have a &lt;em&gt;lot&lt;/em&gt; to learn to become a scientist and a computer programmer but I know you can do it.  This is just the start.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Love,
Damon&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Nuria</name></author><summary type="html">You better write more posts so this one disappears</summary></entry></feed>